You guys are welcome to another video, so in this video we are going to see another kind
of privilege escalation, named it is a powerful access in Windows, it is named as a
C-impersonate privilege, okay, so I will show you what is let me open the command prompt
in an administrator mode and let me check which privileges I have, so now we can find
a few privileged names, here we are going to use a C-impersonate privilege, this should
be enabled, okay, so by default and most of the machines it will be enabled, okay, so let
us discuss what is an impersonate privilege, a C-impersonate privilege, okay, so this is one
of the most powerful mechanism in Windows, so it allows a process to impersonate the security
context of another user, okay, so if you want to start a process you can use a security
context of another user in that process, okay, I mean the higher privilege user security
context into the, which process you are going to create, okay, so this is like it will
be temporarily taking the identity of a higher privileged process and it will be using
that in the current process, okay, so we have set of tools to do this, we have a print
spooler, we have a juicy butter, rotten butter to and row your token manipulation, there
are few tools you can do, but in this video we are going to use one of the tool called
print spooler, okay, let me, you small explanation about the print spooler, okay, so every
computer they it will be connected to the printer, so you can, you can, you can print or scan
remotely, okay, remotely order or a, or a connection, so by using the print spooler software,
our Windows machine will interact with the printer, okay, that's a print spooler, so we
are using the print spooler to exploit this a C-impersonate privilege escalation vulnerability,
okay, basically, so I am going to use this tool, so if you search for K4STH4, print spooler,
this guy has a good tool, print spooler, just download this tool and we need one more
executable called the netcat, so from here you can download the netcat nc.exe 64 or nc.exe
just whichever is feasible, you can download this, okay, so let's keep both of the things
in the same repository, that's your choice, okay, keeping in the same repository or any other
repo, but we'll start working on this, this pretty easy, okay, to elevate the privilege,
let me first use the print spooler, okay, let me show you, we'll execute the, we'll go
to the directory first, okay, we have a print spooler and as I dash C, let me, once again,
so executing this command, let me show you something, so I was in a high mandatory level
of privilege and now I will be executing the, that command print spooler.exe dash
I dash C, CMD, so now it was created process as user, it showed it, okay, and you can
see, we got another CMD, let me view who am I slash hall here, okay, so now you can find
we are in a system mandatory level of privilege, it's a very, very higher privilege, here
you can see everything has been enabled, right, so you can't do any, any sort of things
in a, in a, in a machine, but here you can see a lot of privilege has been, permission
has been disabled, privilege, permission has been disabled, here you can see everything
has been enabled, right, so the reason why I asked you to download the NetCAD, we can take
a reverse connection from this to, it's, it's pretty simple to taking a reverse connection,
let me show you that, to taking a reverse connection, you need a, we will call it an
X machine, let me open up port, name name, all in the LDP, listen, verbos port, 857, let
me, let me open this 856 on port, and let me go to the, let me close these windows, and
I will be using another, let me use another prompt, a certain administrator privilege, so
now here you can see it's, it's like a normal, it's a privilege, it's a high mandatory
level, but not a system level, let me go to redirect to the, okay, so let's use the print
of puller, and we need to, you the command, which command you are going to, we are going
to use, so we are using, so instead of giving the normal CMDR, we are using the NetCAD
here, let me, NetCAD, and you know how to handle a NetCAD, we need to give a IP address of
a listening machine, let me show the IP address here, if, if, I can't say, my IP will be
on 6a dot 18 dot 27, let me, give an IP on and 26a dot 18 dot 27, so now you need to
set up port, which port we are, we have used, it's 8 5 6 7 8 5 6 7 8 5 6 7, and finally, we
can, we can give a CMDR in that end, okay, so let, let me execute this, so now you can
see the create process user as, okay, and here you can see, we got a reverse connection
from that, we can control everything from here in the Kali machine, okay, so we have
a system mandatory level privilege, or we have each and everything to, to handle, right,
so that's all about this video, so another time, so in this privilege escalation, we have
used a SC impersonate privilege to do a privilege escalation, you can find it here, to do
your privilege escalation from administrator privilege to a service account, like a system
account, okay, yes, hope, I have a clear understanding about this video, and we'll continue
our discussion in the next video, see you guys, bye bye.